

Personal Information

Date of Birth: May, 1st, 1986

Age: 33 years **DNI:** 32.359.089

Phone Number: +54 9 (11) 2299-9498

Home Address: Av. La Plata 1058, Piso 12º "G", C.A.B.A.

E-mail: tomas.sande@hotmail.com.ar

Nationality: Argentina Marital Status: Soltero CUIL: 20-32359089-4

Professional Profile

Profession / Area:

I've been developing in support areas for 14 years (specialized in SAP since 2012) characterized by having a pleasant treatment with people, excellent English speaking, leadership capacity and teamwork. I am proactive and adaptable to changes. I'm looking for a position in IT Areas (Maintenance/Project Management).

Professional Experience

Telefonica Global Technology - Buenos Aires Global HR Support Manager

August 2014 - Present

Provide multi-country and cultural HR Support within the whole Telefonica Group

Telefonica Global Technology - Buenos Aires Technical Advisor

January 2012 - July 2014

Guarantee sustainability and best practices of projects and evolution of SAP HCM Systems

Telefónica de Argentina - Buenos Aires Functional Support Analyst April 2008 - December 2011

E' -- l - - l - C - - - - - - - C - - UD D

First level of support for HR Processes

Teleperformance - Buenos Aires Technical Support Representative

June 2005 - December 2007 Technical phone support to AOL, Dell & Vonage US based customers

Education

SAP (HR) Human Resources ECC 6.02 Consultant

SAP Academy by Axigma S.A. 2012

CCNA Modules 1, 2 y 3

Cisco Certified Networking Asociation 2005-2007

Commercial Bachelor

Holy Cross Institute – Bs. As. Argentina 2000-2004

Skills

Skills

Customer orientation Leadership Project Management

Language skills

Native Spanish speaker Advanced English speaker Intermediate Portuguese speaker

IT / Technical / Technological skills

Proficient in using Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Access, Power Point, Project, Outlook)
Proficient SAP HCM consulting (PA, OM, PY)
Proficient Success Factors consulting
Intermediate in programming in C, C++ languages
Intermediate Database administration (Oracle, SQL)
Intermediate Networking administration